New York State Tenants and Neighbors, Inc; Records apap198
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Tenant Organizations & Campaigns, 1973-2000, Undated; 4; 3 cubic ft.
  - 1997 Capaign Rent Guidelines Board (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 32)
  - 1997 Rent Campaign (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 33)
  - Westchester County Rent Guidelines Board, 1998 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 34)
  - Willage of Great Neck Plaza letter from Commissioner of Housing, 2002 May 29 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 35)
  - Ad-Hoc Committee Against Mandatory Rent Deposit, Undated (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 36)
  - City-Wide Task Force on Housing Court, Inc, Undated (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 37)
- Communications, 1973-2000, Undated; 5; 4.4 cubic ft.
  The Communications series is arranged chronologically.
  This series includes information disseminated to New York State Tenants and Neighbors Coalition to New York City tenants in the form of fliers, brochures, leaflets, mailings, legal size posters, etc. The goal of these announcements is to galvanize tenants into a cohesive block that can apply pressure to the legislature by picketing, writing in letters, signing petitions, attending meetings, etc. Other files include NYSTNC Fact Sheets, The files have been arranged chronologically as it's important to note the issues and legislation NYSTNC fought for according to the particular year and the events/bills related to that year.
  - The Golden Years: Housing Opportunities for Senior Citizens, 1973 January (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 1)
  - Rent and Eviction Controls: A Selected Annotated Biography, 1976 June (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 2)
  - Flyers- Various, 1977 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 3)
  - Who Should the Community Development Block Grank Program Benefit- D. Keating, 1977 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 4)
  - NYSTNC Position Paper on New York City Conciliation and Appeals Board, 1978 September 25 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 5)
  - "Manhattan Plaza" by Robert Schur, 1978 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 6)
  - NYSTNC Report on New york City Conciliation and Appeals Board, 1978 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 7)
  - Tenant Resource and Advocacy Center- Center for Study of Responsive Law, 1978 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 8)
  - Chelsea Gay Association Newsletter, 1979 March (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 9)
  - DHCR Housing Workshop and Discussion Paper, 1979 May (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 10)
  - "The Tenants Primer: How to Get the Most from Your Lease" - A. O. Shapiro, 1979 November 26 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 11)
  - "A History of New York State's Tax System"- Annual Report of the Department of Taxation and Finance, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 12)
  - NYPIRG- A White Paper on Iniative/ Referendum, 1979 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 13)
  - New York State Assembly Housing Committee Report, 1979 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 14)
  - NYSTNC Reports on Rent Guidelines Board, 1979 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 15)
  - Tenant Inquilino, 1979-1994 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 16)
  - Housing Tax Shelter Clinic, 1980 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 17)
  - NYSTNC Reports on Rent Stablization Association, 1980 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 18)
  - Planning for the Future of HUD- Owned Housing: a Resident's Guide, 1980 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 19)
  - Flyers- Various, 1981 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 20)
  - NYSTNC- Application to Columbia Foundation, 1981 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 21)
  - NYSTNC Fact Sheets, 1981 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 22)
  - People's Housing News, 1981 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 23)
  - Tax Incentives Provided by New York City Under the 421- A Program, 1981 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 24)
  - Tenants Housing Court Information Booklet, 1982 January (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 25)
  - Tri-State Regional Commission: The Impact of the New Federalism on Housing and Community Development Programs in the Tri-State Region, 1982 March (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 26)
  - Block Grants, the New Federalism, and the Poor: Housing and Community Development- The New Urban Coalition, 1982 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 27)
  - Chelsea Clinton News, 1982 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 28)
  - Comments on Proposed Rent Guidelines Board Order No. 15- Submitted to RGB by NYSTNC, 1983 June 06 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 29)
  - Money for Housing- P. Marcuse, 1983 August 01 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 30)
  - New York City Apartment Law Insider, 1983 August (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 31)
  - Fresh Meadows Tenants Association Newsletter, 1983 August- September (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 32)
  - DCHR Publications, 1983-1986 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 33)
  - Flyers- Various, 1983 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 34)
  - RSA Reporter, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 35)
  - Propaganda Against Vacancy Increase, 1983 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 36)
  - Senior Citizen Rent Increase Exemption, 1983 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 37)
  - Regional Interagency Committee: A Conference to Explore Changes in the Banking Industry and the Impact on Consumers, 1984 January 28 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 38)
  - Hollis Court Tenants Association Newsletter, 1984 February 11 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 39)
  - Cit y Limits, 1984 Febraury- March (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 40)
  - NYSTNC's " DHCR Sins", 1984 September 18 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 41)
  - A Critique of Proposed Rent Stabilization Association Code, 1984 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 42)
  - Small Business Advisory Board, 1984 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 43)
  - Tenants and Neighbors Newsletter, 1984 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 44)
  - Cooperative and Condominium Conversion Handbook, ca. 1984 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 45)
  - NYSTNC Press Conference, 1985 January 29 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 46)
  - Park West Village Associates against City of New York, 1985 April 26 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 47)
  - DHCR Report to the Legislature on the Management of the Office of Rent Administration, 1985 June 15 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 48)
  - In-House, 1985 July- 1986 March (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 49)
  - Empire State Report- "No Vacancy", 1985 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 50)
  - Housing Policy Forum: Will There be Affordable Housing in New York City, 1985 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 51)
  - Koch Rent Guidelines Board Attacks Low-Income Tenants Report, 1985 (Box 1 (5-Communications), Folder 52)
  - Region 2 In View, 1985 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 1)
  - Tenant Alerts and Flyers, 1985 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 2)
  - Tenants and Neighbors Newsletter, 1985-1999 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 3)
  - New York State Budget Policy Statement, 1986 April- 1987 March (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 4)
  - Citizen's Housing and Planning Council " The Assessor", 1986 August (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 5)
  - NYSTNC Brochure and Photographs, 1986 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 6)
  - White Paper Report: "DHCR at the Crossroads", 1987 June (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 7)
  - The Office of Rent Administration: A Management Analysis, 1987 November (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 8)
  - Excessive Charges for Late Rents: A Growing Problem for Upstate Tenants, 1987 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 9)
  - Housing Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 10)
  - Low-Income Housing Round Up and Related Pamphlets, 1987-1993 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 11)
  - The Office of Rent Administration: A Management Analysis, 1987 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 12)
  - NYSTNC Report on Rent Guidelines Board, 1987-1989 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 13)
  - An Analysis of New York City Apartments with Rents of $750 or More, 1988 February (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 14)
  - The ABC's of MCIs, 1988 March (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 15)
  - Ansonia Tenants Coalition Newsletter, 1988 July (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 16)
  - Proposed Office of Rent Administration Organization, 1988 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 17)
  - Tenant Unity Day, 1989 May 16 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 18)
  - Housing and Homelessness: A Teaching Guide, 1989 August (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 19)
  - The Cocoa Courier, 1989 September 15 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 20)
  - Ernst and Whinney: A Review of Major Capital Improvement Program, 1989 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 21)
  - Extending Conversion Protection Throughout New York State, 1989 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 22)
  - Governor Mario M. Cuomo: Message to the Legislature, 1989 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 23)
  - Report to the New York City Rent Guidelines Board, 1990 April 18 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 24)
  - Rent Guideline Board Materials, 1990 May 8 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 25)
  - Tenant Lobby Day, 1990 May 8 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 26)
  - Community Training and Resource Center, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 27)
  - Conference: Exploring Federal Subsidies, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 28)
  - Manhattan Borough: Draft of " Strategic Policy Statement Summaries", 1990 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 29)
  - NYSTNC House Party Article, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 30)
  - Price Index of Operating Costs of Rent Stabilized Apartment Houses in New York City, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 31)
  - A Review of Income and Expense Issues and Recommendations for Research, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 32)
  - Tenant Alerts and Flyers, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 33)
  - Tenants and Neighbors Newsletter, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 34)
  - Rent Control: Facts Not Fiction, 1991 January (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 35)
  - Exploring Federal Subsidies: Education and Mobilization, 1991 February 8 (Box 2 (5-Communications), Folder 36)
  - Supportive Services for Elderly Residents of Government Assisted Naturally Occuring Retirement Communities in New York City, 1991 March (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 1)
  - Taking Rent Control to Court- L. G. Cravitz, 1991 Spring (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 2)
  - National Low Income Housing Coalition Memo to Members, 1991 August (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 3)
  - The City-Wide Task Force on Housing Court Annual Report, 1991 August (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 4)
  - City Limits, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 5)
  - Dismantling Rent Regulations: Fiscal Benefits or Fiscal Disaster- E. Weinstock, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 6)
  - Housing New York, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 7)
  - Housing Insights, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 8)
  - Rent Stabilized Housing in New York City: A Summary of Rent Guidelines Board Research, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 9)
  - Tenant Alerts and Flyers, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 10)
  - Tenant Inquilino, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 11)
  - Empire State Report, 1992 December (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 12)
  - Fact Sheets, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 13)
  - Tenant Alerts and Flyers, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 14)
  - Water Metering, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 15)
  - Governor Mario M. Cuomo: State of the State Address, 1993 January 06 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 16)
  - Stuyuesant Town Tenants Association, 1993 March (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 17)
  - The Latino Journal, 1993 April (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 18)
  - Neighborhood News, 1993 May (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 19)
  - Tarrytown Tenants Association Newsletter, 1993 July (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 20)
  - Housing and Vacancy Survey, 1993 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 21)
  - Housing New York City- A.J. Blackman, 1993 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 22)
  - Low-Income Housing Information Service- National Conference, 1993 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 23)
  - Tenant Inquilino, 1993 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 24)
  - Tenants and Neighbors Newsletter, 1993 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 25)
  - Chelsea Clinton News, 1994 March (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 26)
  - NYRAG Times, 1994 Spring (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 27)
  - ANHD Weekly Reader, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 28)
  - City Limits, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 29)
  - Flyers- Various, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 30)
  - HDFC Coalition Newsletter " Where We Live", 1994 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 31)
  - Landlord v. Tenant, 1994-1996 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 32)
  - Manhattan Institute for Policy Research: A Proposal to Expand Housing and Economic Opportunities by Deregulating America's Rental Housing, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 33)
  - Office of Rent Administration: Report to the Legislature, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 34)
  - Shelterforce, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 35)
  - Tenant Inquilino, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 36)
  - The Task Force on City Owned Property Newsletter, 1995 Summer (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 37)
  - Tenant Action News, 1995 Summer (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 38)
  - Poverty and Race, 1995 September (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 39)
  - EZ/EC News, 1995 October (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 40)
  - Housing Minnesota, 1995 Fall (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 41)
  - News From the Housing Trust Fund Project, 1995 Fall (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 42)
  - Racefile, 1995 November- 1996 April (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 43)
  - Action: Northwest Bronx Community and Clergy Coalition Newsletter, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 44)
  - ANHD Weekly Reader, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 45)
  - City Limits, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 46)
  - Cost Cuts, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 47)
  - The Edna McConnell Clark Foundation Annual Report, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 48)
  - The Landlord Tenant News, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 49)
  - Lower Manhattan Loft Tenants, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (5-Communications), Folder 50)
  - Neighborhood News, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 1)
  - Network News, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 2)
  - Rent Propaganda, 1995 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 3)
  - RSA Reporter, 1995 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 4)
  - Tenant Inquilino, 1995 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 5)
  - Tenants and Neighbors Newsletter, 1995 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 6)
  - The Tenants' Voice Newsletter, 1995 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 7)
  - Hunger Action, 1996 January 15 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 8)
  - Disclosure: The National Newspaper of Neighbors, 1996 January-August (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 9)
  - City Limits, 1996 April 29 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 10)
  - Legal Services Journal, 1996 May (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 11)
  - I'll Be There Jobs With Justice Newsletter, 1996 June (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 12)
  - New York Diminished: The Effects of Budget Cuts on Neighborhood Services, 1996 June (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 13)
  - Housing Environments Research Group, 1996 Summer (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 14)
  - Tenant Times, 1996 Summer (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 15)
  - Mitchell-Lama Resident's Coalition, 1996 September (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 16)
  - Third Force, 1996 September (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 17)
  - Housing Law Bulletin, 1996 October (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 18)
  - The Fair Housing Report, 1996 Fall (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 19)
  - Ahora Now, 1996 Winter (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 20)
  - ANHD Weekly Reader, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 21)
  - Bronx Legal Services Brief, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 22)
  - Council Member Andrew Eristoff Reports to the Community, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 23)
  - City Limits and 20th Anniversary Program, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 24)
  - DC37 Housing Committee Resource Manual, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 25)
  - Flyers- Various, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 26-27)
  - Rebuilding New York's Neighborhoods, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 28)
  - Searchlight on the City Council, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 29)
  - Tenant Inquilino, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 30)
  - Tenants and Neighbors Newsletter, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 31)
  - Tenants Rights and Organizing Conference, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 32)
  - Rent Destabilization Study II- M. Green, 1997 May 18 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 33)
  - Dispelling Information About Rent Controls, 1997 May (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 34)
  - The Daily Packet, 1997 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 35)
  - Flyers- Various, 1997 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 36)
  - Housing Conditions and Problems in New York City: An Analysis of the 1996 Housing and Vacancy Survey, 1997 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 37)
  - Mitchell-Lama Resident's Coalition, 1997 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 38)
  - Tenant Inquilino, 1997 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 39)
  - Tenant Times, 1997 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 40)
  - Vacancy Decontrol, 1997 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 41-42)
  - Mitchell-Lama Resident's Coalition, 1998 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 43)
  - Tenant Action News, 1998 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 44)
  - Tenant Inquilino, 1998 (Box 4 (5-Communications), Folder 45)
  - Tenants and Neighbors Newsletter, 1998 (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 1)
  - Tenant Times, 1998 (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 2)
  - The Tenants' Voice Newsletter, 1998 (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 3)
  - Tenant Alerts and Flyers, 2000 (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 4)
  - ANHD Weekly Reader, 2001 July 13 (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 5)
  - Mayoral Forum of New York City, 2001 July 18 (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, 2001 (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 7)
  - New York City Coalition to End Lead Poisioning- Press Packet, 2002 November 14 (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 8)
  - The Park West Tenant, 2002 June (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 9)
  - Lawyers Alliance for New York Newsletter, 2002 Summer (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 10)
  - Rent 2002- Campaign Materials (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 11)
  - Northwest Bronx Community and Clergy Coalition, Undated (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 12)
  - Myths and Facts about Rent Control, Undated (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 13)
  - Tenant's Manual to Fighting Arson, Undated (Box 5 (5-Communications), Folder 14)
- Audio Visual Materials, 1973-2000, Undated; 6; 1.5 cubic ft.
  The Audio Visual Materials series is arranged chronologically.
  The Audio Visual Materials series contains videotapes with the Tenants and Neighbors Show, NAHT Conferences and other rallies/picketing and politician speeches. Eight U-Matic tapes of the Tenants & Neighbors show is also included within this series.
  - Inside Albany, 1987 May 10; 1987 May 17 (Video-tape 1)
  - Inside Albany, 1992 May 17 (Video-tape 2)
  - Morris & Carrick NYS Democratic Committee "Protect", 1997 April 25 (Video-tape 3)
  - Morris & Carrick New Yorkers to Save Rent Protection "Disaster", 1997 May 14 (Video-tape 4)
  - Governor Pataki Rent Speech, 1997 May 15 (Video-tape 5)
  - Albany Rally Volcanic Video, 1997 May (Video-tape 6)
  - Rent War: Road to City Hall/ On the Line, 1997 May (Video-tape 7)
  - Governor Pataki, Senator Bruno, Member of Assembly Silver: Events in Room 250/ The Capital, 1997 June 15-16 (Video-tape 8)
  - Morris & Carrick New Yorkers to Save Rent Protection "Countdown", 1997 June (Video-tape 9)
  - Rent Wars, 1997 June (Video-tape 10)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Con-Con # 1, 1997 October (Video-tape 11)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Rent Controlled Tenants The Forgotten Minority # 2, 1997 November (Video-tape 12)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show # 3, 1997 December (Video-tape 13)
  - Tenants & Neighbors: Money, Style, and Power, 1997 (Video-tape 14)
  - Rent Campaign 1997 (Video-tape 15)
  - Waffle Breakfast in Albany and Office Interviews, 1998 January 06 (Video-tape 16)
  - "Hells Kitchen Fights Developers", 1998 January 21 (Video-tape 1)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: The Leo house # 5, 1998 Febrauary (Video-tape 2)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: How to Survive Housing Court # 6, 1998 March (Video-tape 3)
  - The Tenant & Neighbors Show: SRO Tenants Unite! # 7, 1998 April (Video-tape 4)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Holding HUD Accountable # 8, 1998 May (Video-tape 5)
  - Picket Pataki, 1998 June (Video-tape 6)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: The 1998 Rent Hike Rip Off # 9, 1998 June (Video-tape 7)
  - Tenants and Neighbors Video, 1998 June (Video-tape 8)
  - NAHT Conference Part 1, 1998 June (Video-tape 9)
  - NAHT Conference Part 2, 1998 June (Video-tape 10)
  - NAHT Conference Part 3, 1998 June (Video-tape 11)
  - T & N Shows, 1998 July (Video-tape 12)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Guiliani's Rent Guide # 10, 1998 July (Video-tape 13)
  - Michael McKee on "Good Day", 1998 August 16 (Video-tape 14)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Tenants to D.C.: Save Our Homes # 11, 1998 August (Video-tape 15)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: The Pitfalls of Subletting # 12, 1998 September (Video-tape 16)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: The 1997 Rent Law- One Year Later # 13, 1998 September (Video-tape 1)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: The Rent 2000 Campaign # 14, 1998 October (Video-tape 2)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Tenant Power at the Ballot Box # 15, 1998 November (Video-tape 3)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Leo House Tenants Evicted The Struggle Continues # 16, 1998 December (Video-tape 4)
  - Tuesday- D. C. Demonstration, 1998 (Video-tape 5)
  - Rent Guidelines Board, 1998 (Video-tape 6)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Housing Court- Worse and Worse # 17, 1999 February (Video-tape 7)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show:Loft Tenants at Risk # 18, 1999 March (Video-tape 8)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Mitchell-Lama at the Chopping Block # 19, 1999 April (Video-tape 9)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Public Housing Saved From Drowning # 20, 1999 May (Video-tape 10)
  - R & B Raw Footage, 1999 May (Video-tape 11)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Taking albany By Storm # 23, 1999 June (Video-tape 12)
  - Tenants & Neighbors, 1999 September 7 (Video-tape 13)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Pitfalls of Subletting # 24, 1999 October (Video-tape 14)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Get the Lead Out # 25, 1999 October (Video-tape 15)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Dangerous Landlord Loopholes # 26, 1999 December (Video-tape 16)
  - Mitchell-Lama Lobby Day, 1999 (Video-tape 1)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Will the City Council Shaft Tenants # 27, 2000 January (Video-tape 2)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show:Loft Law Meets Quick Draw # 28, 2000 Febraury (Video-tape 3)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: # 29, 2000 Febraury (Video-tape 4)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Mitchell-Llama Fights Back # 30, 2000 Febraury (Video-tape 5)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show:Rent 2000: Victory for Tenants # 31, 2000 April (Video-tape 6)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: HUD Tenants Getting It Together # 32, 2000 May (Video-tape 7)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Sublet Guide # 12/24, 2000 July (Video-tape 8)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Renting and Raving # 33, 2000 July (Video-tape 9)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show:Landlords and the Big Lie # 34, 2000 July (Video-tape 10)